Autumn Dreams is a tv movie, romance film directed by Neill Fearnley.
With plans to leave their small town, teenage loves Annie and Ben elope.
Their big city plans are halted, though, when Annie's
parents have the marriage annulled.
Ben moves to New York, while Annie stays in Iowa to help her family.
Fifteen years later, both engaged to their respective fiancés, the
two discover that their annulment was never finalized.
They reunite to make their divorce legal, but begin to
reminisce about what could have been.
When romantic feelings resurface, Annie and Ben must decide if
their past love could be the love of their future.
Annie Hancock, played by Jill Wagner.
Ben Langdon, played by Colin Egglesfield.
Joe, played by Michael Karl Richards.
Jessica Hancock, played by Rachel Hayward.
Jovanna, played by Tasya Teles.
Hal Hancock, played by Ken Tremblett.
Annabella Avery Thorne (born October 8, 1997) is an
American actress, singer, and writer.
She first received recognition for her roles as Margaux Darling in the series Dirty Sexy Money (2007–2008) and as Ruthy
Spivey in the drama series My Own Worst Enemy (2009), the latter of which earned her a Young Artist Award.
Thorne gained prominence for her role as CeCe Jones on the Disney Channel series Shake It Up (2010–2013),
for which she received several awards and nominations, including winning an Imagen Award.
Thorne has since appeared in numerous feature films, including Blended (2014), Alvin and
the Chipmunks: The Road Chip (2015), The Babysitter film series (2017–2020).
She received praise for her roles in The DUFF (2015),
Amityville: The Awakening (2017), and Infamous (2020).
Thorne also led the drama series Famous in Love (2017–2018), for which
she received nominations from the Teen Choice Awards.
Outside of acting, Thorne has ventured into music; she released her debut single,
"Watch Me" in 2011, which charted at 86 on the US Billboard Hot 100.
She has since released the EP Made in Japan in 2012 and the EP Jersey in 2014.
She made her directorial debut in 2019, directing the adult film Her & Him,
which garnered positive reviews and won a Pornhub Visionary Award.
The film explores themes of ex-lover, marriage,
second chance, autumn, fall season.
The tone is emotional.